# **GRENIEL GALINATO**

# </WEB DEVELOPER> </WEB AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER>

Pasig City, Philippines 09951863640

greniel.galinato.com www.grenielgalinato.com

I am a software engineer with hands-on experience in website and system building. I am an enthusiastic developer who is always learning and developing both technical and soft skills, and I am keen to learn about new software technologies that can help the team and business achieve their goals and objectives.

# **Relevant Experience**

#### **Web Developer**

SENCE1 INC

November 2023 - Present

As a Software engineer and Web developer at SENCE1 INC., I'm helping with formulating, planning, and executing new company service ideas. Aside from supporting previous company projects and tasks:

- → I joined two teams for the company service ideas:
  - a. a manpower service idea;
  - b. a scholarship pooling idea.
- ightarrow I helped with the discussions, formulation of design systems, and creation of low and high fidelity wireframes.
- → I'm helping with the frontend development of the service ideas using ReactJS and Material UI. Rails and Laravel for the backend.
- $\rightarrow$  I joined the design team (creating designs for company ID, Calling Cards, and Zoom Background) and analytics team (discussing on how to improve website data gathering and interpretation).
- ightarrow I helped with the creation of the new company website, which included discussion, design creation, site setup, and building.

#### **Web Developer**

CREATIVEHOPE PH INC September 2022 - Present

As a web developer, I'm helping with formulating, planning, and executing new company service ideas. Aside from this, I'm handling multiple coding projects and tasks from our HQ (CREATIVEHOPE INC.) in Japan.

### Junior Web Developer

CREATIVEHOP PH INC
October 2021 - September 2022

## **Skills & Proficiencies**

#### **Programming Languages**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Python C#, PHP, Ruby, SQL

#### **Libraries & Frameworks**

Jquery, React, React Native, Wordpress, Ruby on Rails, Django, Laravel

#### **Tools**

Git, Github, Docker, Postman, Vercel, Netlify, Figma, Adobe Photoshop.

#### **Education**

#### **Divine Word College of Vigan**

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology - March 2016 Graduated with Academic Honors CHED Tulong Dunong Scholarship

# **Tech Certifications**

 Google Analytics Certification -Google

(Acquired: May 2024)

- Foundational with C# with Microsoft - Freecodecamp (Acquired: April 2024)
- AWS Cloud Practioner AWS (Acquired: December 2023)
- Meta FrontEnd Developer Certification - Coursera (Acquired: August 2023)
- Meta Backend Developer Certification - Coursera (Acquired: July 2023)